Now we're going to do a natural smokey crease.
For the natural look, you can skip the crease all together if you want.
We've done enough with the eyes that you can just maybe do a little eyeliner, a little mascara, and you're done.
I just want to show you that you can put a little more oomph into it.
Take a kind of a neutral plumy brown and do a nice crease with it.
This is also the same color I'm going to use as eyeliner.
They're all going to coordinate really pretty.
Again, a little bit goes a long way.
I'm using a crease brush, which is like a pointy fluffy brush.
I'm just going to dip it in ever so lightly.
Just a little a time add this crease color.
The crease color just goes right on the end of the eye.
You basically make a sideways V and you fill it in.
You don't want to go any further than the center of the eye.
You want to kind of keep it concentrated toward the end.
That's what's going to give that cat's eye look, that very natural to dramatic look.
Little by little, depending on how exciting you want go with this look.
Again, you want to keep it natural.
Just add a little bit and a little bit more.
Open.
Keep your eyes open.
Just blend, blend, blend until you get your desired look.
That's about as far as I want to go with it right there.
You can add more and more if you want a little bit more drama.
As far as the natural crease goes, you want to keep it very, very subtle.